♪ Men. ♪
Are you eating
cookie dough?
Yup. It's my favorite recipe.
All you need
is cookie dough and weed.
So the only thing
you have to bake is yourself.
It's very efficient.
It causes the munchies
and then immediately cures them.
(computer chimes)
Hey.
What do you know?
They found my car.
You lost your car?
What the hell's your
cookie dough laced with?
No, I found this company
and they help you
locate old vehicles.
It's called
Dude, Where's My Car?
So what's so great
about this thing?
I don't know. It's my first car.
I got a lot of firsts in it.
First time I learned to drive.
First time I had sex.
First time I had a condom break.
First time I prayed.
So you gonna buy this car?
No. Some guy named
Dirk in Denver has it.
So why go through all the effort
of tracking it down
if you don't want it?
Nostalgia?
It's kind of like...
looking up
your first girlfriend,
or your high school
math teacher.
For me,
those were one and the same.
She still writes me
from prison.
I think my math teacher
had a crush on my me, too.
I mean, why else would he ask me
to take a shower
after math team practice?
Oh, oh, good, everybody's here.
Uh, I would now like
to introduce my girlfriend,
the very fetchin'
Gretchen.
Hey, everybody.
Hi, I'm Walden. It's nice
to finally meet you.
Yeah.
Alan, uh, told me that you work
in an animal shelter
taking in strays.
So we have
a lot in common.
Yeah.
Uh, this is my-my niece Jenny.
Hi.
And we met.
I'm Barry, Walden's
youthful ward.
It's really nice
to meet all of you.
God, this place
is amazing.
How do you afford
the rent, Alan?
(laughs)
What's so funny?
Well, I-I don't pay rent,
per se.
Or per month.
Or per year.
Really? No rent?
How long has that
been going on?
Three years with Walden,
eight years with my dad.
You have been living here
for 11 years for free?
Yeah.
I have never
wanted you more.
(chuckles)
Who's my cheap daddy?
Would you like to see
the bedroom I don't pay for?
Would you like to see my boobs
I bought with a Groupon?
Will you let me get
my grope on?
Nice to meet you, Gretchen.
Make yourself at home.
I've got to stop
saying that.
So, what do you say
we hop on your plane,
head over to Denver
and at least look at this car?
You know you want to.
You guys just want
to go to Colorado
'cause pot is legal there.
What?
It's-It's legal?
They legalized marijuana
in Colorado?
You say up
to three ounces?
Look, we're not going to Denver
to look at a car
and bring home
three ounces of pot.
Yeah, but if we go
with you,
we can bring back
nine ounces.
Fire up the jet.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x21 ♪
Dial 1-900-Mix-A-Lot
Original Air Date on May 1,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
Well, guess who just joined
the Mile High Club.
No, it doesn't count
when you do it alone.
Oh, it counted... twice.
Up top.
No!
Not gonna happen.
This is crazy.
There's no way my old car
is worth the cost
of flying all the way to Denver
and putting in a new bathroom.
We can't turn back now.
I canceled an audition
for this trip.
You're kidding, right?
The part was
Dead Junkie Number Two.
Although, I did buy painkillers
to get into character.
It doesn't matter
what the role is.
This job leads to the next,
and you're playing
Dead Junkie Number One.
And before you know it,
you're playing a live junkie!
And then what?
Win a bunch of Oscars,
get rich, fly around
on a private plane?
Oh, look, I skipped to the end!
So what kind of car
are we going to look at?
You can thank me later
for changing the subject.
It's a 1967 Mustang
with a 289 V-8,
a Holley four-barrel carb
and Positraction.
(whistles)
What does that mean?
I have no idea. My dad used
to say it all the time
when we were working on the car.
I like to think that it
was one of his ways
of saying, "I love you."
Another was,
"Why is Daddy's beer empty?"
I totally get it.
My dad's coded "I love you"
was, "Seriously?
You can't catch a football
one damn time?"
(chuckles)
So you worked on this
with your dad.
Apparently, there's an emotional
connection with this car.
It's a mixed emotion.
It took us two years
to restore it.
When it was finished,
it was cherry.
Of course, Cherry was also
the name of the stripper
that he drove off with
when he left me and my mom.
Wait-- so why would you
want to buy something
that caused you
so much pain?
I mean, that'd be like me buying
the senior prom.
It was on my 16th birthday.
I go outside the house...
and there's that car
sitting in the driveway.
No sign of my dad, though.
It was still the best
birthday ever.
Well, until my mom took a
baseball bat to the windshield.
You know what my dad got me
for my 16th birthday?
A box of condoms and a card
that said,
"Don't make the same mistake
I did."
He was a joker.
How about you, Jenny?
Oh, she would've nailed
Dead Junkie Number Two!
♪ Men. ♪
Oh! What a great idea:
having sex in every
room in the house.
Well, to be fair,
the laundry room was more you
sitting on the dryer
while I took a breather.
Yeah. Next time, I think
I'm gonna throw in
a pair of snow boots.
You know, boom-boom-boom-boom-boom!
Yeah.
One of the advantages
of being here alone.
Kind of makes a man want
to buy a place of his own.
(both laugh)
Nah, I'm gonna die here,
I really am.
So, uh, what do you want
to do tonight?
You know,
besides this guy.
I would love to spend
the night doing this guy,
but we promised Lyndsey and Larry
we'd meet 'em.
Remember, karaoke?
Oh, that's right.
Oh, hey, hey,
maybe we can use
my Halloween costumes
from last year.
You know, Donny and Marie?
Although I'm not sure you'd fit
into Walden's Donny outfit.
You know, I was thinking
tonight would be a great time
to tell Larry that you're
not Jeff Strongman,
that you're really
Alan Harper.
Oh, that's funny
because I was thinking
tonight might be a great night
to not ruin four people's lives.
He's my brother, Alan.
I can't just
keep lying to him.
I lied to my brother all
the time. It worked out great.
Your brother's dead.
I didn't say it worked out
great for everybody.
♪ Men. ♪
(plays discordant chord)
Hey!
Are you Dirk?
Are you a cop?
No.
Then I'm Dirk.
I'm Walden Schmidt.
I called about the car.
Actually, on the phone,
you asked if I was a cop.
And then you asked me
if I wanted to buy any weed.
Yeah, that's the right order
to ask those questions.
I learned that the hard way.
These your kids?
(snickers)
No.
Are they mine?
Hey, uh, is this the car?
Yeah, let me take her
top off for you.
You're about to see one hot car.
Where, behind
this piece of crap?
She's not that pretty,
but she gets the job done.
Just like my old lady.
Hey, that's not bad.
♪ She's not that pretty,
but she gets the job done ♪
♪ I'd like to escape,
but I'm too old to run! ♪
Yeah, that's a hit!
So is this your car?
Yeah.
It's still got the Vote For Bush
bumper sticker on it.
You were a Republican?
No, my friends and I
just thought it was funny.
You know, "Bush"?
Tell you what, I love Bush.
You and me both.
She's got a lot
of wear and tear on her.
Not much to look at.
Looks like it was rear-ended.
Just like my old lady.
But she's got new headlights
and a roomy backseat.
Just like your old lady?
Hey! That's the mother
of three of my five kids!
Anyway, this bad boy can still
get up to a buck ten.
Yeah, maybe if the truck
towing it was going 110.
You don't believe me,
I refer you
to World's Wildest
Police Chases, episode 139.
Whoa, what died in here?
My granddad.
The seat belt got jammed,
we had to
leave him in there
for a couple of days.
Okay, well, hey, thank you
for showing us the car.
Whoa, hang on, hang on.
How much do
you want for it?
Uh, uh, uh, what are you doing?
I'll take $1,800 unless you can
come up with some kind
of other arrangement.
Ew!
How about you?
No!
$1,800 it is, then.
I'm not...
I'm not buying this car.
Walden, this car
is a piece of your life.
It doesn't mean anything
to anybody else
in the world except you.
All right, I'll give you $1,800.
Dude, you didn't haggle.
It's no good unless you haggle.
Okay, uh, fine. $1,600.
$1,700.
Deal. $1,700.
Yeah!
I was just gonna give you
$1,800.
That's the thing
about haggling, dude.
Sometimes you win,
sometimes you lose.
We definitely have to get
some of this guy's weed.
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Hey, will you love me
forever? ♪
♪ Let me sleep on it
♪ Will you love me forever?
♪ I couldn't take it
any longer ♪
♪ Lord, I was crazed
♪ And then the feeling came
upon me like a tidal wave ♪
♪ I started swearing to my God
on my mother's grave ♪
♪ That I would love you
till the end of time ♪
♪ I swore I'd love you
till the end of time! ♪
Yeah!
Gretchen, Jeff!
Follow that, bitches.
Come on, Lyndsey, it's our turn.
♪ Who let the dogs out?
Woof, woof. Woof, woof.
Come on. You can do
better than that.
Larry, do I look like I want
to do better than that?
Ooh, last time I saw
that face,
I forgot
to pick up wine.
Boy, was I in
the doghouse
that night. Hey!
♪ Who's in the doghouse?
♪ Who-who-who-who?
That's what
I'm talking about!
Come on. Let's show 'em how
you and your brother
do it doggy style.
He doesn't really
hear himself, does he?
Why are you here?
I've told you a hundred times,
I don't want
to double-date with Gretchen
and Jeff Strongman.
Well, you won't
have to anymore.
Guess who's gonna tell Larry
the truth tonight.
♪ Who-who-who-who?
What do you mean?
I told Gretchen
who I really am.
I was tired of living a lie
and sneaking around,
being dishonest.
I'm better than that.
She caught you.
Yes. Yes, she did.
But it felt good
to get it off my chest.
If you tell Larry
who you really are,
then he's gonna wonder why
I didn't tell him.
And that's not something
I want to deal with
less than two weeks before
we're supposed to get married.
God, is it two weeks?
Boy, I better find
those rings.
Alan, you're not gonna say
a thing about
who you really are.
I'm sorry, but I already
promised Gretchen.
And-and the fact
of the matter is
you and I aren't
in a relationship anymore,
so you no longer have me
by the balls!
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Dial 1-900-mix-a-lot
and kick them nasty thoughts ♪
♪ Baby got back!
(cheering)
Come on, Larry, let's
show 'em how we do it.
There you go!
Menstrual cramps
can't stop my lady!
It's Larry-oke time!
♪ Ow! I feel good
♪ I knew that I would now
So, did you talk
to Larry yet?
Uh, well, you know,
I was, I was running
this whole thing by
Lyndsey, and, um...
Whoa, wait. Why would you
run it by Lyndsey?
You know, she is the
one getting married,
and I didn't want
to spring it on her
because Lyndsey is not the
girl you want to get angry
unless you're about
to have sex with her,
'cause then she
turns into a freak,
and I don't know
why I'm saying this.
I know why.
Because you still have
feelings for her.
(scoffs) That's crazy.
I just, I think
it's the right thing to do,
that's all.
Oh, my God.
That is why you invented
Jeff Strongman
in the first place,
was to win Lyndsey back.
Feelings like that
don't just disappear.
Sure, they do.
There's a lot of things
I used to love that
I don't love anymore:
uh, roller coasters,
dairy, my mother.
This isn't funny, Alan.
Well, I-I was just saying...
No, listen to me.
Look, if you want to run
everything by your ex-girlfriend
and not tell Larry the truth,
then so be it.
But I don't want anything
to do with it. Or you.
Wait, Gretchen...
Gretchen. Gretchen, wait!
♪ I feel good
♪ I knew that I would now
Come on, Jeff,
you know the words.
♪ So good, so good
♪ I'm gonna die alone
♪ Ow!
♪ Men. ♪
Aren't you glad
I made you do this?
Yeah.
Having déjà vu.
My dad used to let me sit
on his lap and steer.
Yeah, my dad
wasn't around much.
I had to teach myself all those
things that dads teach you:
how to ride a bike,
how to shave,
how to change a tire,
how to masturbate.
What?
No, dads don't teach you
how to masturbate.
I'm glad somebody told me
before I had kids.
This thing is actually
really cool.
What made you sell it
in the first place?
I needed the seed money
to start my company,
and it's the only thing
I had that was worth anything.
You know,
when you think about it,
this car is really responsible
for everything I have:
the beach house,
my jet and my fortune.
Alan.
Shh, she didn't mean it.
It's not true.
So that means your dad
is kind of responsible
for your success, too,
doesn't it?
I never really thought of it
like that.
I guess he is.
Thanks, Dad.
Oh, that gave me the chills.
Oh! No, wait.
There's a hole
in the floorboard.
Anybody else want to
drive for a while?
I don't know how to drive.
What?
I grew up in Manhattan.
I've been in taxis and cop cars.
Ooh, this is my first time
in the front seat!
Well, there's no time
like the present.
(all screaming)
I'm gonna pull
in here.
I'm pretty sure they sell underwear
at Cracker Barrel.
♪ Men. ♪
Berta?
Hey, Zippy.
It's 10:00.
What are you still doing here?
It's 11 years later.
What are you
still doing here?
Where's your girlfriend?
Gone. I think I lost her.
You mean "lost"
like you broke up
or "lost" like the time Charlie
took Jake to Disneyland?
Broke up.
Wait-- Charlie lost Jake?
Actually, Jake lost Charlie.
Security found him.
He was doing white snow
with Snow White.
So, um,
what did you do to drive
this girlfriend away?
She thinks I'm still
in love with Lyndsey,
which I'm not,
but she doesn't believe me.
Well, make her believe you.
You can make anybody believe
anything.
You made the IRS believe
you had seven dependents.
That's true.
I went to chiropractic college
on an NAACP scholarship.
Exactly.
And you made those people
at the movie theater
believe that you were under 14.
And over 65.
Once on the same day.
(laughs)
The, uh, the secret is
that both of those groups wear
little baseball caps.
(laughs)
I was saving this
for your funeral,
but, Zippy, you're a charmer.
Thanks, Berta.
No. Thank you.
Now I don't have
to go to your funeral.
♪ Men. ♪
Wow,
this Utah sky is amazing.
We're indoors.
Wow, this Colorado weed
is amazing.
Guess who just joined
the 6,106-foot club.
It doesn't count
when you do it alone!
Whatever.
I don't like it here.
There's no Wi-Fi
or cell service.
It's like one of those movies
where you find out
the little town's full
of zombies.
Or werewolves.
Or zombie werewolves.
How would that happen?
Hello. Do the math.
Zombie bites a werewolf,
werewolf dies, comes back
as a werewolf zombie.
That's a badass,
unkillable creature.
He's right. Chain the door.
Wait a second. You think
chaining the door
is gonna stop
a zombie werewolf?
I'll tell you what,
I'm not gonna be the guy
who gets killed by
a zombie werewolf
'cause I didn't chain the door.
(laughs)
Hey...
thanks for coming with me, guys.
And I'm not just saying that
'cause I can use you
as human shields
when the zombie werewolf
breaks in the door.
Yeah, I'm really
glad we came, too.
And about almost
killing you guys
in the car earlier--
that's my bad.
Yeah, well, I am glad
that Cracker Barrel
had underwear.
And these "I Heart Denver"
sweatpants.
You know, this is still better
than that family trip
I took to Utah
as a kid.
My dad was trying
to convince my mom
to add another wife
to the family.
Started the trip
with one wife,
tried to get two,
came home with zero.
Hotel had
a great pool, though.
At least you knew
your dad.
I barely knew Charlie.
I got one letter from him
my entire childhood.
It said, "Are your
friends 18 yet""
Yeah, hearing you guys talk
about your dads,
and thinking about mine,
makes me question even wanting
to have kids.
You already have kids.
(Walden laughs)
Papa.
Come on. I'm not your dad.
You've been a better dad
to me than anybody ever has.
You-you-you took me in,
you inspired me to be
a better person.
You pushed me to be
a dead junkie.
I really want that for you, too.
She's right, man.
You're a role model.
I mean, you believe that
I can make something
out of myself
and you stopped me
from going to prison
for teaching my son
how to masturbate.
That's right.
You want to be a hands-on dad,
but not too hands-on.
Hey, bring it in, kiddos.
Oh!
Aw...
(laughs)
Oh, Dad?
Hmm?
Barry's got his hand
on my butt again.
It's not my hand.
Okay.
All right.
♪ Men. ♪
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Gretchie.
I don't want to talk
to you right now.
Gretchen's still mad at you,
but I'm on your side, Jeff.
Bros before hoes.
Oh, uh, oh, good, you're,
uh, you're all here.
Because I have something
to say...
to everyone.
Are you sure, Jeff?
Some things
are better left unsaid.
I love you so much,
I-I can't imagine
my life without you.
Just stop.
Maybe this will help.
Okay, I appreciate the gesture,
but looking for change together
isn't gonna work this time.
The only change I want is
for us to be husband and wife.
ALL:
What?!
Gretchen Martin,
will you do me the honor
of becoming Mrs. Alan Harper?
Oh, my God!
My sister and my best...
Wait a minute.
Who the hell is Alan Harper?
Larry, look, boobs!
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, look at you.
You're doing great.
You haven't hit
a guardrail in miles.
Once you get
the hang of it,
this driving thing
isn't so tough.
How about after I restore it,
I give it to you?
What? You love this car.
I've gotten what
I need out of it,
and I'd rather have it
stay in the family.
Who better to have it
than my my...
sort-of-daughter.
Aw! You're the best
sort-of-dad ever!
Whoa! Hands on the wheel!
Hands on the wheel!
(tires squealing)
Whoa!
Why are you yelling at me?
You should be
yelling at them
for driving on
the wrong side...
(all scream)
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man